

Sarah Haddad

Visual Computing Graduate



About Me

Visual Computing I am a graduate specializing computer vision and image processing. My passion lies in AI, web development, and design. In my free time, I enjoy coding and working on web projects.



Contact



+213659334939



sara.-haddad@outlook.fr



SARAH-HADDAD



Sarah-HADDAD-IT



Skills

Python/ Flutter/ OpenCV/ Blender/ Unity/ C#/ Firebase/ Java/ Dart/ Figma/ C/ JavaScript/ GitHub/ Html/ Css/ TensorFlow/ pandas/ React.js / numpy/ vueis



Language

- Arabic
- French
- English
- Kabyle

Education

(2019 - 2022)

UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND **TECHNOLOGY HOUARI BOUMEDIENE**

Bachelor's in Academic Computer Science

(2022 - 2024)

UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY HOUARI BOUMEDIENE

Master's in Visual Computing



Experience

(2021 - 2023)

COMPUTER VISION INTERN

CERIST

Developed a 3D reconstruction method specifically designed for complex bridge structures using computer vision.

(2022 - 2023)

GAME DEVELOPER

Micro Club

Modeling in Blender, coding in Unity for VR games.

(2021 - 2023)

MEMBER OF IT SECTION

Micro Club

Working on an IT event.